Hi, guys. Today, I will guide you on how to add a proxy to change your IP using the Proxy
Helper extension. First, go to the Chrome Web Store and install the Proxy Helper extension.
After installing, click on this icon and pin the extension.
Right-click and select Options to open Proxy Helper. This is the interface of the tool,
it looks very simple, right? I'll introduce the features of Proxy Helper one by one.
In the General section, Proxy Helper supports proxies for four protocols, HTTP,
HTTPS, SOC S, and QUIC. Use the protocol that fits your proxy and fill in the
information in the corresponding section. If you're not sure which type your proxy is,
just fill in all four sections. Next is the Proxy Mode. There are five different types,
Single Proxy, Proxy for HTTPS, Proxy for HTTP, Proxy for FTP, and Fallback Proxy.
You can just select the default option, which is Single Proxy.
If your proxy has a username and password, go to the authentication
section to enter that information. You only need to set these two sections,
and you're done. Now, let's go to IP Fighter to check the new IP address.
Just select HTTP Proxy. After selecting the correct proxy protocol, refresh the IP Fighter page.
The IP address and location have changed. So, you've successfully added the proxy.
If this proxy can't access the internet, try the other protocols to see which one works.
There are also other options like Auto Detect, this automatically detects proxy
settings from the system or network. For example, if you're using a VPN or have
set up a proxy on your computer, it will automatically catch the IP based on those settings.
System, this uses the system's proxy settings.
Direct, this accesses the website without using a proxy.
You can add the extension to different Chrome profiles to change the IP for each one.
For example, I added Proxy Helper on another Chrome profile with a US Proxy.
Just follow the steps I just showed you to add and access it.
Now, the two profiles have different IP addresses and locations.
Additionally, Proxy Helper has a Bypass List feature in the Rules section, which allows
users to set certain websites to access without using a proxy, instead using the original IP.
For instance, instead of using IPv4, you can use IPv6 to manage your Facebook accounts more
efficiently. However, some of Facebook's payment services aren't fully compatible with IPv6 yet.
So when you add a payment card while creating an ad campaign, you might run into errors.
In this case, by adding websites to the list, when you need to link a bank card,
the system will use your original IP without going through the proxy, helping you bypass
the website quickly without switching back to IPv4. That's how to use Proxy Helper to change
proxies and fake your IP on the Chrome browser. You can use this extension on Edge profiles or
use Foxy Proxy for Firefox. Thank you for watching the video. Wishing you all the best.